

PERSONAL INFORMATION



Surname: MitevForename: Stanislav

Nationality: Bulgarian

Gender: MaleDOB: 01/30/1987

Age: 31

Status: Married Religion: Christian

Address: Flat 2 Brockwell, Fore street, Seaton, Devon,

EX12 2AD

Telephone: 07586053560Email: s.mitev@hotmail.com

Personal	Statement
reisuliai	Statement

I am 31 years old. I am a hard working, trust worthy and reliable individual. I enjoy meeting new people and developing new skills. I learn quickly and can follow instructions. I work well in a team or by myself using my own initiative. I work calmly when under pressure and am able to meet deadlines. I am a positive person with a good sense of humour.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Name and address of employer	Home Grown Hotels
Type of business or sector	Hospitality
Dates	August 2017- Present
Occupation or position held	Kitchen Porter
Main activities and responsibilities	 Ensure basic cleaning jobs are carried out as quickly as possible. Collect and wash up pots and pans. Clean food preparation areas and equipment, in addition to crockery and cutlery. Unload food and equipment deliveries. Keep the storeroom organised. Keep work surfaces, walls and floors clean and sanitised.

Name and address of employer	Venian Limited
Type of business or sector	Delivery Systems
Dates	August 2016- August 2017

Occupation or position held	Night shift lead driver/supervisor
Main activities and responsibilities	Courier night driving. Supervision of the night shift fleet on the ASOS site. Detail reporting to company director, customers and clients. Monitoring the night shift fleet, checking vans, organisation of servicing of the vans. Daily rota for driver destinations. Supervision of correct loading of parcels. Liaison with management to resolve issues.

Name and address of employer	XPO (Previously NDL Norbert Dentressangle)
Type of business or sector	Global on-line fashion retailer (ASOS)
Dates	March 2014 – Present date
Occupation or position held	Warehouse Operative (Picking & Packing)
Main activities and responsibilities	 To work flexible long hours including shifts when requested. To work in a fast pace environment and perform to high expectations and achieve targets set by my team leader. I pick goods from the warehouse to fulfil orders of the retail market and satisfy deadlines for dispatch. When orders are complete I deliver the trolley to a team member who packs the orders.

Name and address of employer	'Face' Bar & Restaurant, Sofia, Bulgaria
Type of business or sector	Tourism / Restaurants
Dates	June 2011 – March 2014
Occupation or position held	Head Bartender
Main activities and responsibilities	 Reporting to Food & Beverage Manager. Responsible for Organizing Bar Area Supervisor of a Team of 2 (Two) bartenders. Managing Bar Sales - (Soft Drinks, Coffees and Alcoholic Beverages). Responsible for Bar Area Budget. Coordinating of Wine List and Beverage Menu Cards. Managing Sales of Wine and Spirits. Responsible for Stock Control and Ordering. Responsible for Training and Partners Evaluation. Managing Bar Marketing Activities.

Name and address of employer	Kraft Foods Bulgaria
Type of business or sector	Marketing

Dates	September 2009 – May 2011
Occupation or position held	Merchandiser
Main activities and responsibilities	 Maintaining daily contact with the staff at the sites. Responsible for the proper positioning of the items. Loading of goods. Monitoring expiry dates and availability at the sites. Preparation of panel's price of goods in the product group. Preparation of daily reports of the merchandising.

Name and address of employer	'Skyline' Coffee & Restaurant, Sofia, Bulgaria
Type of business or sector	Tourism / Restaurant
Dates	May 2008 – October 2009
Occupation or position held	Waiter & Bartender
Main activities and responsibilities	 Responsible for Organizing Restaurant Bar Area In charge for Bar Stock Control. Responsible for ordering. Managing Bar Sales - (Soft Drinks, Coffees and Alcoholic Beverages). Responsible for Bar Area Budget. Serve as waiter in restaurant (take orders, serve food, clear tables). Clean restaurant (wipe tables, vacuum floor). Prep restaurant for next shift (fill condiments, roll silverware, etc.). Clean wait station (wipe counter, clean soda/coffee/juice machines). Serve customers and work with other staff in friendly/courteous/helpful/professional manner.

EDUCATION & TRAINING

Dates / Qualifications /	• 2001 – 2006, High School Diploma
Place of Study	High School Louis Pasteur, Sofia, Bulgaria

FOREIGN LANGUAGES & ADDITIONAL SKILLS

Foreign Languages	 English – Very good level. Can speak, write and read very well
Additional Skills	 PC skills: Microsoft Office, Internet, Software and hardware skills. Good ability for team work

Responsible
Good communication skills
 Self-motivated, organised, hard worker, commit to work and always ready
for a challenge
A good memory
Have good physical health

HOBBIES & INTERESTS

Hobbies & Interests	 Fishing Reading Surfing on the Internet Computer building Sports Music
---------------------	---